tirerack.com 2000-06-06

# The Tire Rack - Ordering Info - Privacy Statement

**YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS PRIVATE**

The Tire Rack is serious about protecting our customers’ personal information. You can always browse our Web site without providing any personal information.

While doing business with you, we may have to gather certain information, such as your name, home address and e-mail address. We will not sell, rent, trade or give away individual, personally identifiable information entered on this site to any third party (except that if you enter this information on our co-branded site reached through BrandsForLess.com, we may share this information with BrandsForLess.com). We collect such information so that we can process orders, personalize your shopping experience, or send you the latest product and other useful material. If you do not wish to receive further material from The Tire Rack, you can simply respond to our e-mail or otherwise tell us that you do not want to receive future communications.

**ONLINE ORDERS**

The Tire Rack also collects credit card information from you to process purchases from the site. Reputable third-party financial institutions handle our credit card transactions

Whenever you transmit credit card information and other personal information through our site, the numbers and letters are scrambled using encryption technology, making it nearly impossible for the information to be stolen or intercepted. To protect your security, we do not allow you to store your credit card number from session to session.

**COOKIES**

The Tire Rack, like most Web sites, uses a feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your computer. We cannot tell your name or any personal information about you based solely on the cookie. Unless you specifically tell us your name and other identifying information, we will never know who you are. All the cookie tells us is what you do - meaning what functions you perform - when you are on the site so that we can keep track of your transaction. A cookie also helps The Tire Rack note particular traffic patterns on the site so that we can improve what we offer.

Every browser allows you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies you will accept. Doing so, however, may sometimes interfere with your ability to use all the features of The Tire Rack site. If you choose not to allow cookies, you may not benefit from the special features offered by the site

**THIRD PARTIES**

On occasion, we provide non-personal, aggregate information about our users to third parties such as manufacturers and business partners. For example, we may inform a tire manufacturer about what other products its users buy. This information will not identify any user personally.

**OUTSIDE LINKS**

The Tire Rack may offer links to other sites. Any time you click on a link and are transported to another site, you should be aware that the other site may have a different privacy policy than The Tire Rack. We cannot control the policies of other sites.

**CHANGES**

This privacy policy is subject to change at the sole discretion of The Tire Rack. When we modify it, we will post the changes in a revised policy statement.

**HOW ARE WE DOING?**

We value your business and want to deserve your trust. If you have comments, questions or suggestions, please let us know at [sales@tirerack.com](mailto:sales@tirerack.com)
